Hello!
We are Terry and Laura Neven.
I am the administrator of California educators and principal of Sunland Christian School.
This clip we will talk about the benefits to home schooling.
Many families begin to home school not because of concerns of academics or because of concerns of the local public or private school because they are concerned about things relative to the family.
Home schooling can provide a great opportunity for family unity.
To do things together, to learn together and to grow together.
In specifically Southern California there is a lot of issues relative to a flexibility of schedule.
It is important to understand that home schooling allows for great flexibility.
Moms are already running around like chickens with their heads cut off, taxing kids here and there.
When you teach your children at home, it allows you a greater opportunity to have time as a family.
One important reason for the benefit of home schooling is academic success.
Researh says that the average home school child is 1 to 2 grades levels above their public or private school peers.
These are just some of the wonderful benefits why families home school.